pdftoexcel.com 2015-09-07

# Convert PDF to Excel - Free Trial

Your privacy is important to Investintech.com Inc. ("Investintech"). This statement discloses the information practices for the Investintech website, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. We respect your right to privacy and we recognize the trust you are placing in us through your dealings with us. As such we do everything we can to maintain that trust.

Under law your rights to privacy are also protected. The law places strict requirements on us to treat any information you give us as confidential. The information you provide remains private and is only used for the purposes outlined below.

In general, you can visit Investintech on the Internet without telling us who you are and without giving any personal information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you.

You may choose to give us personal information in a variety of situations. For example, you may want to give us information, such as your name and address or e- mail id, to correspond with you, to process an order, or to provide you with a subscription. You may give us your credit card details to buy something from us (please note that this information will not be stored on our website or that of our third party provider other than to process the transaction itself) or a description of your education and work experience in connection with a job opening at Investintech that you wish to be considered for. We intend to let you know how we will use such information before we collect it from you; if you tell us that you do not want us to use this information to make further contact with you beyond fulfilling your requests, we will respect your wishes. If you give us personal information about somebody else, such as a spouse or work colleague, we will assume that you have their permission to do so.

If you request something from the Investintech Web site, for example, a product or service, a callback, or specific marketing materials, we will use the information you provide to fulfill your request. To help us do this, we may share information, with others, for instance, other parts of Investintech, Investintech's business partners, financial institutions, shipping companies, postal or government authorities (for example, Customs authorities) involved in fulfillment. In connection with a transaction we may also contact you as part of our customer satisfaction surveys or for market research purposes.

We intend to protect your personal information and to maintain its quality. We implement appropriate measures and processes, such as using encryption when transmitting certain sensitive information, to help us to keep your information secure and to maintain its quality.

If you have a question about this statement, you can send an email to the Investintech privacy officer who is also our President. His e-mail address is [dave@investintech.com](mailto:dave@investintech.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Question). You can also contact us at this address if you have a question about Investintech's handling of your information, if you wish to obtain a copy of particular information you provided to Investintech, or if you become aware the information is incorrect and you would like us to correct it. Before Investintech is able to provide you with any information or correct any inaccuracies, however, we may ask you to verify your identity and for other details to help us to respond to your request. We will endeavor to respond within an appropriate timeframe.

If you believe we have breached your privacy rights in any way, or you would like to discuss any issues about our privacy policy please contact our Privacy Officer. We will try to satisfy any questions that you have and correct any errors on our part.

This Web site is maintained by Investintech.com Inc. This privacy statement was last updated on November 22nd, 2003. A notice will be posted on our Web site home page for 30 days whenever this privacy statement is changed in a material way.
